Guide to the Greenwich House Records TAM.139
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Programs
  - Subseries A: Departments and Activities
    - Sub-subseries 68: World War II Work
      - Newsletter to GH Servicemen; List of Servicemen, 1941-1945 (Box 26, Folder 72)
      - USO/American Women's Volunteer Service, 1941-1942 (Box 26, Folder 73)
    - Sub-subseries 69: Works Progress Administration
      - WPA School of Human Relations, undated (Box 26, Folder 74)
      - WPA Workers' Correspondence, 1933-1942 (Box 26, Folder 75)
      - WPA Workers (CWA Workers) Report, undated (Box 26, Folder 76)
    - Sub-subseries 70: Youth Council
      - Youth Council-correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 26, Folder 77)
      - Youth Council- report, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 78)
      - Youth Council- constitution and minutes, 1944-1946 (Box 26, Folder 79)
  - Subseries B: Special Events
    This subseries contains very special and unusual ephemera, including programs, tickets, flyers, posters, as well as some correspondence, for benefits, anniversaries, holidays and other special events. Among these were the several Metropolitan Opera performances for the benefit of Greenwich House, and variety shows starring such actors as Marie Dressler and John Barrymore. Simkhovitch's close relationship with Eleanor Roosevelt, who settled in the Washington Square area after she left the White House is reflected in this subseries. Other people close to Simkhovitch were Fiorello LaGuardia and Herbert Lehmann. Each lent name as patron to benefits and special events, and participated when possible.
    - Sub-subseries 1: Anniversaries
      - 25th Anniversary Dinner, 1928 (Box 27, Folder 1)
        Reel 34 (MN #2215)
      - 30th Anniversary- invitation to celebrations, 1932 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - 35th Anniversary- congratulatory letters, 1937 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - 35th Anniversary- Simkhovitch Portrait-Correspondence with Painter, 1937 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - 35th Anniversary- Simkhovitch Portrait-Contribution Correspondence, 1937 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - 35th Anniversary- Simkhovitch Portrait-Contribution Correspondence, 1937 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - 35th Anniversary- Simkhovitch Portrait-Contribution Correspondence, 1937 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - 35th Anniversary- Simkhovitch Portrait-Contribution Correspondence, 1937 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - 35th Anniversary- Simkhovitch Portrait-Contribution Correspondence, 1937 (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - 35th Anniversary- Simkhovitch Portrait, 1937 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - 35th Anniversary- Simkhovitch Portrait- Committee Fundraising Letters and List, 1937 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - 35th Anniversary- clipping from Villager, 1937 (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - 40th Anniversary- publicity materials, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - 40th Anniversary- correspondence, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - 40th Anniversary- invitations, speeches (LaGuardia, Field, Simkhovitch), 1942 (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - 40th Anniversary Calendar of Events, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - 40th Anniversary- invitations, programs, newspaper articles, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Sub-subseries 2: Benefits
      - Benefit Performance- Morning Musicale, Waldorf-Astoria, 1909 (Box 27, Folder 18)
      - Benefit Performance- Pantomime & Dance, Waldorf-Astoria, 1910 (Box 27, Folder 19)
      - Benefit Performance- Variety Show, Plaza Hotel, 1913 (Box 27, Folder 20)
      - Benefit- Dance, Sherry's, New York City, 1914 (Box 27, Folder 21)
      - Benefit Performance- Variety Show, Selwyn Theatre, 1919 (Box 27, Folder 22)
      - Benefit- Vaudeville Ball, Waldorf-Astoria, 1920 (Box 27, Folder 23)
      - Benefit Entertainment and Ball, Hotel Pennsylvania, 1920 (Box 27, Folder 24)
      - Benefit- Jamboree, Greenwich House- correspondence, 1932 (Box 27, Folder 25)
      - Benefit- Jamboree, Greenwich House- reports & finances, publicity, lists of contributors, 1932 (Box 27, Folder 26)
      - Benefit- Garden Party, Field Estate, Long Island, 1934 (Box 27, Folder 27)
      - Benefit- Dance & Bridge, Hotel Pennsylvania, 1934 (Box 27, Folder 28)
      - Benefit- Dance & Bridge, Hotel Pennsylvania- correspondence, 1934 (Box 27, Folder 29)
      - Benefit Performance "Joseph and His Brethren", 1934 (Box 27, Folder 30)
      - Benefit- Garden Party, Field Estate, Long Island, 1935 (Box 27, Folder 31)
      - Benefit- Tour of Greenwich Village gardens, 1936 (Box 27, Folder 32)
      - Benefit- "Evening Under the Stars," Rockefeller Center Patron and Guest Lists, 1936 (Box 27, Folder 33)
      - Benefit- "Evening Under the Stars," Rockefeller Center, 1936-1937 (Box 27, Folder 34)
      - Benefit Performance- Hansel & Gretel/The Bat, Metropolitan Opera House, 1936-1937 (Box 27, Folder 35)
      - Benefits- Spring Garden events, Greenwich Village, Long Island, 1937 (Box 27, Folder 36)
      - Benefit Performance- Hansel & Gretel/The Bat, Metropolitan Opera House, 1937-1938 (Box 27, Folder 37)
      - Benefit Performance- Casey Jones, Fulton Theatre, 1938 (Box 27, Folder 38)
      - Benefit- Spring Garden events, 1938 (Box 27, Folder 39)
      - Benefit Performance- Hansel & Gretel/Pagliacci, Metropolitan Opera House, 1938-1939 (Box 27, Folder 40)
      - Benefits- Spring Garden events, 1939 (Box 27, Folder 41)
      - Benefit Performance- Jooss Ballet, Alvin Theatre, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 42)
        Reel 35 (MN# 2216)
      - Benefit- Garden Party, Field Estate, Long Island, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 43)
      - Benefit- Gala Children's Carnival, Hunter College, correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 27, Folder 44)
      - Benefit- Gala Children's Carnival, Hunter College, programs, reports, patrons list, 1941 (Box 27, Folder 45)
      - Benefit- Garden Party, Field Estate, Long Island, 1941 (Box 27, Folder 46)
      - Benefit- "Valentines for Victory" Dinner and Dance, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 47)
      - Benefit- "Night of Stars" Party, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 48)
      - Benefit- Preview and Buffet Supper, Little Carnegie Theatre programs, tickets, minutes, financial report, patrons list, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 49)
      - Benefit- Preview and Buffet Supper, Little Carnegie Theatre correspondence, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 50)
      - Benefit Performance "Janie", 1943 (Box 27, Folder 51)
      - Benefit- Open House on Historical Macdougal Alley for the Greenwich House Camp, 1964 (Box Shared Tamiment MSOS003, Folder 1)
        General
        Item not microfilmed
      - Benefit- Flower and Ceramics Show and Sale for the Greenwich House Pottery Scholarship Fund, 1967 (Box Shared Tamiment MSOS003, Folder 1)
    - Sub-subseries 3: Holidays
      - Christmas Celebrations, 1910-1916 (Box 27, Folder 52)
      - Christmas Celebrations, 1921-1946 (Box 27, Folder 53)
      - Thanksgiving Celebrations, 1914-1917 (Box 27, Folder 54)
      - Thanksgiving Celebrations, 1925-1932 (Box 27, Folder 55)
      - Thanksgiving Celebration, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 56)
      - Thanksgiving Celebration, 1941 (Box 27, Folder 57)
      - Thanksgiving Celebration, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 58)
      - Thanksgiving Celebration, 1944 (Box 27, Folder 59)
      - Thanksgiving Celebrations, undated (Box 27, Folder 60)
    - Sub-subseries 4: Other events
      - Special Events- Calendars, 1939, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 61)
      - Special Events- programs, invitations, 1911-1940 (Box 27, Folder 62)
      - Special Events- invitations, programs, undated (Box 27, Folder 63)
      - Special Events- Spring Pageant and Robin Hood play, 1909 (Box 27, Folder 64)
      - Special Events- Mackenzie Boat Ride, May 21, 1915 (Box Shared Tamiment MSOS003, Folder 1)
      - Tea Parties, 1926-1928 (Box 27, Folder 65)
      - Teas for Workers, 1930-1931 (Box 27, Folder 66)
      - Children's Theatre Tea, 1931 (Box 27, Folder 67)
      - Special Events- Meetings of Unemployed Workers and Artists, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 68)
      - Special Events- Forums- Report, 1938-1939 (Box 27, Folder 69)
      - Special Events- Pan-American Dinner and Concert, 1939 (Box 27, Folder 70)
      - MKS Retirement- correspondence, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 71)
      - MKS Retirement- press releases, speeches, seating list, program, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 72)
      - MKS Fund for Greenwich House established, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 73)
      - Special Events- Antique Chic Show and Sale, 1979 (Box Shared Tamiment MSOS003, Folder 1)
  - Subseries C: Publications
    This subseries dates from the early days of Greenwich House and contains reports, minutes, correspondence (principally Simkhovitch), and various other materials. These are all organizations of which either Simkhovitch or Greenwich House was a member. Greenwich House was a member of Association of Neighborhood Workers, United Neighborhood Houses, Greenwich Village Improvement Society, etc. Simkhovitch was member and often officer of groups such as the Public Recreation Commission, Parks and Playgrounds Association of NYC, National Public Housing Conference (NPHC). The main theme of this material is Simkhovitch's personal struggle to make the Village a better place for her working-class and poor neighbors and to unite the Village as a real community rather than submit to the normal anonymity of city life. Her concern extended beyond her own neighborhood, as membership in such organizations as the NPHC shows. Highlights of this materials include Greenwich House involvement in setting aside land in Greenwich Village for public parks, clearing out of then red-light Minetta district, and decisions made over the south extension of 7th avenue.
    - Sub-subseries 1: Greenwich House Publications
      - Publications describing Greenwich House & activities, undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Publications describing Greenwich House & activities, 1918-1921 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - "The Tenants' Manual", 1903 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - "A West Side Rookery", 1906 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - "Public Art Education in New York", 1908 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - "Old Age Poverty in Greenwich Village", 1915 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - "Greenwich Village Directory", 1918 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - "Greenwich Village Directory", 1920 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Greenwich House Songs from 1921 Contest (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - Directory of Greenwich Village- Drafts, 1923 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - "Greenwich Village Social Directory", 1924 (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - "Longshoremen and their Homes", 1939 (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - "Greenwich Village Directory", 1942 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Sub-subseries 2: Newsletters
      - "The Village Bell", 1914 (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - "Greenwich House Bulletin", 1915 (Box 28, Folder 15)
      - "Listening In", 1927, undated (Box 28, Folder 16)
      - "Tuning In", 1927-1933 (Box 28, Folder 17)
      - "Town Meeting Crier", undated (Box 28, Folder 18)
      - "The Play Log", undated, ca1942 (Box 28, Folder 19)
      - "The Green and White", 1945-1946 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Subseries D: Register of Visitors to Greenwich House
    - Register of Visitors to House, 1920-1943 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Subseries E: Outside Organizations (Alphabetical)
    - All Day Care of Children, 1917 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      Reel 36 (MN# 2217)
    - Artists' Aid Committee- Outdoor Exhibits, 1932-1933 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Association of Neighborhood Workers- Arts & Festivals Committee, 1908-1912 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Association of Neighborhood Workers- Spring Festival, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Association of Neighborhood Workers- Committee on Central Office- minutes, appeal, 1916 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Association of Neighborhood Workers- Committee on Education- minutes, 1916 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Association of Neighborhood Workers- Committee on Highways- correspondence re street cleaning, 1914-1915 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Association of Neighborhood Workers- Committee on Highways- reports re street cleaning, 1914-1915 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Association of Neighborhood Workers- Tenement House Committee, 1903 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Association of Neighborhood Workers- Conference on Boys' Work, 1916 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Association of Neighborhood Workers- Constitution & By Laws, undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Association of Neighborhood Workers- Correspondence, 1915 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Association of Neighborhood Workers- Correspondence, 1916-1918 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Association of Neighborhood Workers- Financial reports, 1916, undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Association of Neighborhood Workers- Lists of officers, head workers & member houses, 1915, undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Association of Neighborhood Workers- Minutes, 1911-1916 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Association of Neighborhood Workers- Publications, 1915-1917 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Association of Neighborhood Workers- Reports, 1918, undated (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Association of Neighborhood Workers- Resolutions, 1915, undated (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Barnett Memorial Fellowships, Oxford; Jane Addams, 1925-1926 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Church League for Industrial Democracy, 1941, undated (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Citizens' Committee of America, 1922-1924 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Citizens' Committee on Building Trades Issues in NYC, 1923 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Citizens' Housing Council of New York, 1942 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - City History Club of New York, 1906-1928 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Civic Education Committee- Monthly reports, 1922-1924 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Civic Education Committee- Correspondence, 1922-1925 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - College Art Association- Exhibit, 1932 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Commission on the Social Function of the Church, 1923 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Committee of Fourteen- Correspondence, 1917-1924 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Committee of Fourteen- Minutes; member lists, 1924-1927 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Committee of Fourteen- Reports, 1924-1929 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Committee on National Aid to Education- Correspondence, 1916-1917 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Committee on National Aid to Education- Minutes, 1916-1917 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Committee on National Aid to Education- Reports, Bill for Congress, 1917 (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - Community Councils of Greater New York, 1919 (Box 29, Folder 36)
    - Consumers' Emergency Council, 1937-1938 (Box 29, Folder 37)
    - Council on Immigrant Education- Executive Committee minutes, 1923-1926 (Box 29, Folder 38)
    - Department of Health- Committee on Public Health minutes, 1914 (Box 29, Folder 39)
    - Equal Franchise Society- member list, 1908-1911 (Box 29, Folder 40)
      Reel 37 (MN #2218)
    - Greater New York Emergency Conference on Inalienable Rights, 1940 (Box 29, Folder 41)
    - Greenwich Commission- correspondence, 1914-1916 (Box 29, Folder 42)
    - Greenwich Commission- minutes, resolutions, 1915-1916 (Box 29, Folder 43)
    - Greenwich District Committee- member list, 1914-1915 (Box 29, Folder 44)
    - Greenwich District Community Council, 1919 (Box 29, Folder 45)
    - Greenwich Village Association- constitution, 1925 (Box 29, Folder 46)
    - Greenwich Village Association- newsletter, 1941 (Box 29, Folder 47)
    - Greenwich Village Association- member list, undated, ca1941 (Box 29, Folder 48)
    - Greenwich Village Association- carol sing, 1932 (Box 29, Folder 49)
    - Greenwich Village Association- Study on City Planning correspondence, 1935-1936 (Box 29, Folder 50)
    - Greenwich Village Association- Study on City Planning minutes, report, 1935-1936 (Box 29, Folder 51)
    - Greenwich Village Association- Village Fair, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 52)
    - Greenwich Village Association- Annual Dinner, 1938 (Box 29, Folder 53)
    - Greenwich Village Neighborhood Annual Conferences, 1940-1942 (Box 29, Folder 54)
    - Greenwich Neighborhood Conference, 1941 (Box 29, Folder 55)
    - Greenwich Village Neighborhood Conference, 1942 (Box 29, Folder 56)
    - 4th Annual Greenwich Village Conference, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 57)
    - 5th Annual Greenwich Village Conference, undated (Box 29, Folder 58)
    - 6th Annual Greenwich Village Conference, 1945 (Box 29, Folder 59)
    - Greenwich Village Improvement Society- Announcements, Flyers, 1913-1915, undated (Box 29, Folder 60)
    - Greenwich Village Improvement Society- correspondence, 1913 (Box 29, Folder 61)
    - Greenwich Village Improvement Society Old Home Week- Minutes, 1913 (Box 29, Folder 62)
    - Greenwich Village Improvement Society Old Home Week- List of Clergy Invitations, 1913 (Box 29, Folder 63)
    - Greenwich Village Improvement Society Old Home Week- List of Speakers at Opening, 1913 (Box 29, Folder 64)
    - Greenwich Village Improvement Society Old Home Week- New York City Department of Education Report and Program, 1913 (Box 29, Folder 65)
    - Greenwich Village Improvement Society Old Home Week- Poems, 1913 (Box 29, Folder 66)
    - Greenwich Village Improvement Society Old Home Week- Correspondence (April - May 15), 1913 (Box 29, Folder 67)
    - Greenwich Village Improvement Society Old Home Week- Correspondence (May 16 - May 31), 1913 (Box 29, Folder 68)
    - Greenwich Village Improvement Society Old Home Week- Correspondence (June and undated), 1913 (Box 29, Folder 69)
    - Greenwich Village Improvement Society Old Home Week, 1913 (Box 29, Folder 70)
    - Greenwich Village Improvement Society Old Home Week- Register- "Ye Old Times of Greenwich Village (longtime Village residents), 1913 (Box 29, Folder 71)
    - Greenwich Village Improvement Society- Greenwich Village Fair Programs, Flyers, Press Release, 1914 (Box 29, Folder 72)
    - Greenwich Village Improvement Society- Greenwich Village Fair Baby Parade- list of entries, entry blanks, 1914 (Box 29, Folder 73)
    - Greenwich Village Improvement Society- Greenwich Village Fair Correspondence (March - April), 1914 (Box 29, Folder 74)
    - Greenwich Village Improvement Society- Greenwich Village Fair Correspondence (May), 1914 (Box 29, Folder 75)
    - Greenwich Village Improvement Society- Greenwich Village Fair Correspondence (June and undated), 1914 (Box 29, Folder 76)
    - Greenwich Village Improvement Society- Greenwich Village Fair Minutes, Permits, Committee reports, 1914 (Box 29, Folder 77)
    - Greenwich Village Improvement Society- Greenwich Village Carnival correspondence, 1915 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Greenwich Village Improvement Society- Greenwich Village Carnival minutes, 1915 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Greenwich Village Improvement Society- Greenwich Village Carnival posters, programs, etc., 1915 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Greenwich Village Week- Preliminary Planning, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Greenwich Village Week- Speech by Alfred E. Smith, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Greenwich Village Week- programs, flyers, announcements, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Greenwich Village Week- correspondence, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Greenwich Village Week, 1934 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Inter-Settlement Dramatic Society, 1917 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      Reel 38 (MN# 2219)
    - Joint Fundraising- Executive Committee, 1933 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - League for Industrial Democracy, 1938-1947 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Lower West Side Council- minutes, 1930 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Lower West Side Council of Social Agencies, 1943-1946 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Lower West Side Council of Social Agencies- constitution, by-laws, minutes, structure & function, member lists, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Lower West Side Defense Council, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - National Association of Housing Officials-Continuation Committee, 1934-1937 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - National Consumers' League- Label Committee, 1917 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - National Federation of Settlements- General Correspondence, 1915-1917 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - National Federation of Settlements-Questionnaire on Settlement Program for Wartime, 1917 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - National Federation of Settlements-Subcommittee on Constructive Peace, 1915 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - National Federation of Settlements-Study of the Pre-Adolescent Girl, 1916-1917 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - National Federation of Settlements- 5th Conference, 1915 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - National Federation of Settlements- 6th Conference Minutes, Outlines, 1915-1916 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - National Federation of Settlements- 6th Conference Correspondence, 1916 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - National Federation of Settlements- 6th Convention, 1916 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - National Federation of Settlements- 7th Conference correspondence, list of delegates, report, 1917 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - National Federation of Settlements- 8th Conference, 1918 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - National Federation of Settlements- 10th Conference, 1920 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - National Federation of Settlements, 1934-1936 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - National Federation of Settlements, undated, ca.1936-1944 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - National Federation of Settlements, 1937 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - National Federation of Settlements, 1938-1940 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - National Federation of Settlements, 1941-1942 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - National Federation of Settlements, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - National Federation of Settlements, 1944 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - National Federation of Settlements- membership list, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - National Federation of Settlements- personnel practices, 1944 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - National Federation of Settlements, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - National Federation of Settlements, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 39)
    - National League for Woman's Service, 1917 (Box 30, Folder 40)
    - National Public Housing Conference-certificate of incorporation, constitution and by-laws, 1936-1943 (Box 30, Folder 41)
    - National Public Housing Conference-lists of members of Board of Directors and Advisory Committee, 1941-1944, undated (Box 30, Folder 42)
    - National Public Housing Conference- correspondence, 1932-1935 (Box 30, Folder 43)
    - National Public Housing Conference- correspondence, 1936-1941 (Box 30, Folder 44)
    - National Public Housing Conference- correspondence, 1942-1944, undated (Box 30, Folder 45)
      Reel 39 (MN# 2220)
    - National Public Housing Conference-memoranda, press releases and statements, 1932-1944, undated (Box 30, Folder 46)
    - National Public Housing Conference-memorands, reports and statements, 1940-1942, undated (Box 30, Folder 47)
    - National Public Housing Conference-Federal Public Housing Legislation Conference transcript, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 48)
    - National Public Housing Conference- Articles by Simkhovitch, Louis Pink, Maxwell Tretter, 1936-1938, undated (Box 30, Folder 49)
    - National Public Housing Conference, 1936-1940 (Box 30, Folder 50)
    - National Public Housing Conference- summary of discussion at Secretary of the Interior's Conference, 1937 (Box 30, Folder 51)
    - National Public Housing Conference grant application to the New York Foundation, 1937 (Box 30, Folder 52)
    - National Public Housing Conference- Address by Jan Bommer, National Housing Council of the Netherlands, 1939 (Box 30, Folder 53)
    - National Public Housing Conference- 9th Annual Meeting, 1940 (Box 30, Folder 54)
    - National Public Housing Conference- 10th Annual Meeting, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 55)
    - National Public Housing Conference-proposed Amended United States Housing Act, 1944 (Box 30, Folder 56)
    - National Public Housing Conference- financial records, 1934-1942 (Box 30, Folder 57)
    - National Public Housing Conference- minutes, agendas, 1933-1944 (Box 30, Folder 58)
    - National Unemployment League-chronology, statement of purpose, 1931, 1936 (Box 30, Folder 59)
    - National Unemployment League- circulars, press releases, 1930-1937 (Box 30, Folder 60)
    - National Unemployment League- correspondence, 1931-1938 (Box 30, Folder 61)